

BIRTHDAY:

19/06/1999

NATIONALITY:

ITALIAN

LICENCE:

B

ADDRESS:

Via San Pio X 208 TV 31033 (ITALY)

PHONE:

+39 389 290 3924

EMAIL:

sergioallushaj@gmail.com

SERGIO ALLUSHAJ

I specialize in front-end development with experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Next js. I focus on creating modern, responsive, and highly functional websites that offer a unique design and an exceptional user experience. View my current projects on :

https://vanta-black-website.vercel.app/

EDUCATION

99/2013 - 07/2018

DIPLOMA: AUDIOVISUAL
PRODUCTIONS IPSIA GALILEO
GALILEI

- Technical and theoretical study of photography.
- In-depth exploration of photographic language through the study of cinema history, art, and advertising, with the aim of acquiring a wide range of skills covering all aspects of the audiovisual world.
- Professional training in videomaking.
- Training in the use of professional audio, video, and software equipment for various types of audiovisual productions (interviews, commercial videos, sports events, graphics, performances, mini-documentaries, videos dedicated to urban and natural landscapes).

05/2023 - ONGOING

WEB DEVELOPMENT AND DESIGNER COURSE, ACCADEMIA DELLE PROFESSIONI, PADUA, ITALY

Currently studying HTML5, CSS4, JavaScript, and jQuery for front-end development and using Figma to study responsive and

user-friendly principles for web application prothotipying. Utilizing Photoshop, Illustrator and After Effects for design and animation tasks like personalized logos, icons and creation of video motions.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2021/12 - 2022/08

CUSTOMER SERVICE - STOREDEN (TV)

Dedicated technical assistance to customers by providing support in case of bugs or errors on the Storeden e-commerce platform or the website. Modifications to websites using JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Twig, Bootstrap 4/5.

2022/12 - 2023/02

JUNIOR BACK-END DEV - ESOSPHERA (RS)

Developed web applications using PHP with the Yii2 framework, relational databases, and PostgreSQL.

2023/05-2023/10

JUNIOR FULL-STACK DEV - W-EASY

Development and maintenance of websites and management services for companies using the following technologies: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, and PHP.

"I authorize the processing of my personal data contained in the CV in accordance with art. 13 of Legislative Decree 30 June 2003 n. 196 - 'Code regarding the protection of personal data' and art. 13 GDPR 679/16 - 'European regulation on the protection of personal data'"

Castelfranco Veneto, 27/06/2024

Sergio Allushaj